A: Do you have any brothers or sisters?
B: I have one sister.
A: I have one brother, Adam.
B: Oh cool, tell me about him.
Is he like you?
A: No, he’s very different.
He’s quite a bit older than me, he’s thirty-one.
B: What does he look like?
A: So, he’s quite tall.
He’s not overweight, but I’d say he’s well-built
– he goes to the gym a lot.
He had dark curly hair when he was younger,
but now he doesn’t really have any hair, he’s bald.
I think he’s good-looking – he has big dark eyes, and he’s very warm and friendly,
he always has a smile on his face.
What about your sister?
What’s her name?
B: She’s called Melanie, but we all call her Mel.
A: Does she look like you?
B: A bit.
She’s not very tall, I suppose about one metre seventy,
and she’s normal weight, not thin, but slim.
She has very long hair, blonde, and she has green eyes.
A: What’s she like? I mean, as a person?
B: She’s quite quiet and serious,
but when you get to know her she’s actually very funny.
A: Do you think she and Adam would get on?
B: Perhaps?
Let’s all have dinner together one day, you, me, and Adam and Mel.
A: Good idea.